[Music]
bonjour welcome to another product
review now this is dedicated to the noo
now this was lovingly bought for me by
my dad last Christmas and I open the box
and I looked inside and I
thought so can't be bothered with that
cuz I've got a razor that's really easy
to use the instruction manual comes with
its very own
CD anything that requires its own CD to
use is never going to fly by me I mean
look at the chunkiness of that
instruction manual so that to me is a no
no so the idea of this product is that
it gets rid of your hair with ease um
I'll just show you what it's what what
the components are and then you can tell
me whether you think it's with ease
we've got a plug a weird little thing
like a cloth no idea what that is it's
like a biscuit thing what else have we
got I think those must be the razors
I've never actually taken this out of
its box and looked because I just opened
it and thought I definitely can't be
bothered with that which I feel bad
about because I've now looked up how
much it cost and and it's around £100
and my poor dad never really had a
proper thank you because I didn't quite
realize how much money he spent on it
and there's the No No there it is and
it's full Glory oh look there's
something else there's something else
hiding down there there's a tiny tiny
tiny little
brush like look at this this upsets me
yeah I'm supposed to Fathom all of this
just so that I can have silky smooth
legs so that I can be a goddess and
bring out the goddess within me well
actually
I'm already a goddess with massive hairy
legs
so
anyway so that's the Box we'll put that
away now I shaved my legs quite recently
so I'm not a good person to test it on
but I do have someone here with very
very hairy legs he's going to help
me oh look at this fa so okay so we have
to take that off that's the No No to
plug it in okay so we'll get one of
these I mean it's got different
consisten I don't
know what a
f so that's the
razor does that go in
there I me okay so that's
that I'm going to have to read the
instructions arry so the best so that's
that so now I've plugged my no no in and
I've put the raise a bit in and now I I
don't there's no on button there's no I
really want to be able to do this
without reading the instructions cuz I
personally think if something is user
friendly you shouldn't have to read a
booklet really it was a bit arrogant of
me but I just think design it well so
there isn't an on button so I press this
every time I press that the razor comes
out which I think is maybe part of it
maybe it's oh oh oh it does something
weird it's kind of hot and fiery okay I
need your leg all
right so this is my brother's leg he's
kindly volunteered so let's see what
happens you
ready
oh oh oh
so no hair is actually being removed but
there's a burning there was that was
smoke and wow that is stinky so that I
think from what oh stinky so from what I
can tell it just burns the hair off wow
did that hurt no not at all no no did it
no no you want to give it another couple
yeah come on let's give it a
go here we go
I think you have to do it a few times I
mean there's smoke there's smoke okay
oh I can't be doing it right I can't be
doing it right there was loads of hair
in there it's coming off mate it is
coming up so not bad 10 10 seconds 10
seconds I'm sorry I think when when
smoke start starts to come off your leg
you know it's time to read the
instructions
so I did read the instruction manual my
favorite chapter was chapter five no
before you no
no
so yes the No No essentially singes your
hair off it burns your hair off and
because of all of the faf and the fact
there's a little hair like little hair
brush that you need to like clean it
with every two or three swishes
and because it's just such a faf and it
needs to be connected to the mains I
would like to give this product a minus
one out of
10 however there is a bit of a caveat
because it does kind of
work thanks to the no no my brother now
has a a BAL patch on his leg but the
whole room stinks of burnt hair and and
and his hand does as well he's touched
the burnt hair so I would I would say
that maybe that's a one out of 10 if you
really love the smell of burnt hair and
faf and wires and tiny tiny little
brushes so thank you Dad so much for
this present because it's been really
fun and I've enjoyed doing this review
and burning my brother's leg hair but I
think probably um next year I'd really
like a tie
[Music]
a